Guide to the Tom Law San Francisco Bay Area Punk and Rock Handbill and Poster Collection M1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes and 1 large map folder
  - Folder 24, 1983- 1986 (Box 1)
    9. The Flow; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; March 24 -- The Flow; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; March 25; 8.5x11.
    10. Fountains Of Use; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-05; 8.5x11.
    11. Altar De Fey, The Nuns; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-03; 8.5x11.
    12. Ravage, Elf; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; May 12; 8.5x11.
    13. Patsy Cline & The Memphis G Spots; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-13; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 25, 1985- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Schrödinger's Cat, [illegible], Black Athletes, Faith No More; [illegible]; San Francisco, CA; March 30; 8.5x11.
    2. The Proper Shoes, Fallen Angel, Distant Relatives; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-04; 8.5x11.
    3. Ju Ju Bach; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-13; 8.5x11.
    4. Jr. Walker & The Allstars, Katie Webster & The Uptighters; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-31; 8.5x11.
    5. Judy Mowatt, Vision; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-13; 8.5x11.
    6. Joe Liggins & The Honeydrippers, Katie Webster; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-17; 8.5x11.
    7. Dance Hall Style Sound System Clash. MLK Birthday Celebration To Benefit The Reggae Calendar; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-19; 8.5x11.
    8. Zula Pool, Elements Of Style; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-15; 8.5x11.
    9. Rhythm & Noise; "For Location Information Please Call…"; San Francisco, CA; 1983-12; 8.5x11.
    10. Kor-Phu, Rhythm Pigs, Speed Queens, Clown Alley; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-23; 8.5x11.
    11. Misled; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; December 26 -- Misled; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; December 18; 8.5x11.
    12. The Descendents, D.R.I., The Boneless Ones, Insurgency; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-09; 8.5x11.
    13. Jet Boy, Poison, Mikki Shields; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-31; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 26, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Model Americans; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-12; 8.5x11.
    2. No Visible Means Of Support; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; May 14; 8.5x11.
    3. [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; April 30-May 4; 8.5x11.
    4. Tripod Jimmie, Dot 3; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-02; 8.5x11.
    5. The Vicelords, Spot 1019; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-10; 8.5x11.
    6. The Cat Heads, Jon Gon, World Wayoutz; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; October 17; 8.5x11.
    7. The Sleepers (Ricky Williams Ordeal), American Music Club (Mark Eitzel Ordeal); On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-20; 8.5x11.
    8. Swans, Trial; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-12; 8.5x11.
    9. Rhythm Pigs, Short Dogs Grow, Kor-Phu; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; November 12; 8.5x11.
    10. Sex Farm; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; May 9; 8.5x11.
    11. Sybil; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; July 7; 8.5x11.
    12. Savage Republic, Black Athletes, Slovenly; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25; 8.5x11.
    13. Noize Boyz; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA -- Noize Boyz; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 27, 1984- 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    1. Funhouse [Funkhouse], P. Zuzu & K. Komo; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-18 -- Funhouse [Funkhouse], Thieves' Cross; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; August 19; 8.5x11.
    2. Frightwig, Camper Van Beethoven, Glorious Din, Shiva Dancing, M.J.B.; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-01; 8.5x11.
    3. Eyes Of God; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-02; 8.5x11.
    4. Victim's Family, Crash n' Burn, Mudwomen; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-26; 8.5x11.
    5. Amok; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St; San Francisco, CA; December 27; 8.5x11.
    6. Until December, Strappado; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06; 8.5x11.
    7. Nova Mob (Formerly Ha Ha); 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-27; 8.5x11.
    8. Wombat Suicide, The Miracle Workers, Safe Insane, KFJC DJ Ransome Youth; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-22; 8.5x11.
    9. Tripod Jimmie; [many]; San Francisco, CA; April 1-29; 8.5x11.
    10. Tyranny And Structure, A State of Mind, Victim's Family, Raining House; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-11; 8.5x11.
    11. Ten Tall Men, American Music Club, The Naked Into, 3 Mouse Guitars; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-15; 8.5x11.
    12. The Morlocks, Sea Hags, The Whitefronts; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-15; 8.5x11.
    13. Gemini Party for Michelle & Christopher. Come As your Alter-Ego; 1310 Page St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-06-09; 8.5x11.
    14. Scratch At Moscow; Spirit Club; 1130 Buenos San Diego, CA; Every Wednesday; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 28, 1982- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Dive In; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-31;8.5x11
    2. Dive In; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; August 1; 8.5x11.
    3. De Laria. Raging Bull; Valencia Rose; 766 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; Thursdays & Fridays in May; 8.5x11.
    4. The Descendents; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-16; 8.5x11.
    5. The Witnesses, Tekno Fear, Jex; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-11; 8.5x11.
    6. Bardo; 160 Shrader St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-21; 8.5x11.
    7. Toy Dolls, Jet Boy, Sea Hags; The Keystone; 260 S. California Ave Palo Alto, CA; 1986-01-20 -- Jet Boy, Tramp; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-26 -- Toy Dolls, Jet Boy; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-19; 8.5x11.
    8. Blake Nelson; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; March 9; 8.5x11.
    9. Dynatones; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; September 1; 8.5x11.
    10. Altar De Fey, Thrill Of The Pull; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; October 31; 8.5x11.
    11. Anvil Chorus, Griffin, Reign; Old Waldorf; 444 Battery St. San Francisco, CA; 1982-10-25; 8.5x11.
    12. Gunner Robinson, Jim Wigler; The Stables; 1123 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; October 6-31; 8.5x11.
    13. Toxic Reasons, House Of Wheels, Rhythm Pigs; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; April 26; 8.5x11.
    14. Costumeness. Old Clothes.; The Black Cat; 418 Hayes St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 1, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. The Offenders, The Dicks, Condemned To Death; Valencia Tool & Die; 974 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-15; 8.5x11.
    2. Executive Slacks; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-30; 8.5x11.
    4. The Cat Heads, The Whitefronts; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-04; 8.5x11.
    5. Snakefinger's Vestal Virgins, The Ophelias, Ten Tall Men; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-03-29; 8.5x11.
    6. The Whitefronts, Vomit Launch, Terra Incognita; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-04; 8.5x11.
    7. The Whitefronts; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15; 8.5x11.
    8. The Whitefronts; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15; 8.5x11.
    9. Vile Under Vile; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-26; 8.5x11.
    10. Vicious Hippies; Starry Plough; 3101 Shattuck Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-01-24 -- Vicious Hippies; Last Day Saloon; 406 Clement St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-12 -- Vicious Hippies; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-17; 8.5x11.
    11. City Of Industry; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; October 9; 8.5x11.
    12. Beat The Fat Cat Ronnie Reagan By...Voting [etc.] [handwritten]; San Francisco, CA; 1984; 8.5x11.
    13. Yo, The Naked Into, Sea Hags, The Cat Heads; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-19; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 2, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. The Whitefronts, Next To Nothing [Nexto Nothing]; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-01; 8.5x11.
    2. The Witnesses; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-20; 8.5x11.
    3. Wombat Suicide; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-04 -- Wombat Suicide; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-26; 8.5x11.
    4. Lucas, New Language, Monkey Rhythm, Performance Artists: Ogieiocha; Yamoto Drums, Rex Bruce; Minx Gallery; 64 Gough St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-13; 8.5x11.
    5. The Whitefronts, Next To Nothing [Nexto Nothing], The Spamtones; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-01; 8.5x11.
    6. Whorl, Earwaves, Metro Sensuous; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-28; 8.5x11.
    7. Vulgar and The Woodcutter; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-24; 8.5x11.
    8. Wombat Suicide; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-05; 8.5x11.
    9. Fallen Angel, The Defectors; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-16; 8.5x11.
    10. Fallen Angel, The Afflicted; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-15; 8.5x11.
    11. Fade To Black; Fountains Of Use; Orange Curtain; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-25; 8.5x11.
    12. Fade To Black; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-18; 8.5x11.
    13. Kommunity FK, Black Athletes, Shiva Dancing, Thrill Of The Pull, Darkside of Pop [?]; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 3, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Youth Brigade, Rhythm Pigs, Christ On Parade, Rabid Lassie; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 8.5x11.
    2. Dot 3; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-25; 8.5x11.
    3. Zef, Mr. White, Guitar; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-17; 8.5x11.
    4. Zula Pool; The San Francisco State. Depot; 1650 Holloway Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-08; 8.5x11.
    5. Box O' Laffs; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-06-15 -- Box O' Laffs; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15 -- Box O' Laffs; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-06-06; 8.5x11.
    6. Zasu Pitts Memorial Orchestra; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-02; 8.5x11.
    7. Blue Movie; The Lab [Co-Lab]; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-08-02; 7x10.5
    8. Deer Rose; 8th Street Studio; 2525 8th St. Berkeley, CA; April 26, 27 & May 3,4 -- Deer Rose; Gumption Theatre; 1563 Page St. San Francisco, CA; May 9-25; 8.5x11.
    9. Jim James; The Stud; 1535 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; Nov. 11 [reception]; 8.5x11.
    10. Brain Rust, Misfits In a Jungle Of Buildings, Paranoid Blue, 23 Screams; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-28; 8.5x11.
    11. Robert Seidler, Zula Pool; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-13; 8.5x11.
    12. Black Magic, Rhythm Rockers, Next To Nothing [Nexto Nothing]; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-01; 8.5x11.
    13. Agent Orange, D.I., Sea Hags, House Of Wheels; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-01 -- Agent Orange, D.I., Christ On Parade, Rhythm Pigs; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-01; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 4, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Godzilla Voice. Written and Directed by Alex-5, Performed By Alex-5, Jay DeBaun and Johnny Perfect Land; Bibliomantic Book Gallery; Haight St. Near Fillmore St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12; 8.5x11.
    2. Z; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; August 21, 28; 8.5x11.
    3. Bwana Devils, Davenports; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-09; 8.5x11.
    4. Cult Of Bigness; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-05; 8.5x11.
    5. Dot 3; Thin White Rope; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA;1986-01-18; 8.5x11.
    6. The Contractions, Big City, Jungle Dinner; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1984-02-17; 8.5x11.
    7. American Music Club, Dot 3; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-05; 8.5x11.
    8. Bandaleers; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-06; 8.5x11.
    9. Missing July 1. $50.00 Reward. Cockatiel [etc. with drawing of bird]; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    10. Hootenanny With Members Of Cat Heads, Blue Movie, The Furies, The McGuires, Terra Incognita & Very Special Pals; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    11. [advertisement]; Subterranean Records; 577 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    12. The Dream Syndicate, Ape Cult; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1984-08-28; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 5, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. The Cat Heads, Slovenly; Spot 1019; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-12; 8.5x11.
    2. The Cat Heads, Camper Van Beethoven; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; August 22 -- The Cat Heads, Camper Van Beethoven; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; August 23; 8.5x11.
    3. The Cat Heads, Mrs. Green; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06 -- The Cat Heads, Flying Color; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06; 8.5x11.
    5. The Cat Heads, The Whitefronts; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-04; 8.5x11.
    6. Crash Puppies; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; December 20; 8.5x11.
    7. Hanging Party, Code Of The West, Boss Hoss, G.T. Jesus; [Capp Street Center]; 362 Capp St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-19; 8.5x11.
    8. [Caroliner Rainbow?]; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-06; 8.5x11.
    9. The Cat Heads, The Bwana Devils, Pleasant Day, The Ophelias, Love Circus, Three Mouse Guitars, Ricky Williams, Morticia; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 8.5x11.
    10. Burning Witches, Heroine, Boy Trouble; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; April 19; 8.5x11.
    11. Xeno, Evil; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-03; 8.5x11.
    12. Burning Witches, The Volunteers; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-31; 8.5x11.
    13. Zulu Spear, Image; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-27; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 6, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. The Thrones, Caroliner Rainbow Botulism Pregnancy, Half Blind; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-04; 8.5x11.
    2. Grupo Cultural, One World Beat DJ Jonathan E.; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-21; 8.5x11.
    3. Caribbean Allstars; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-21; 8.5x11 -- Until December; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-24; 8.5x11.
    4. Look; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-04; 8.5x11.
    5. Caroliner Rainbow Benza Passover, Babysitters From Hell, Victim's Family, Snotgreen Sea; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; December 7; 8.5x11.
    6. Bardo, Blue Movie; The Lab [Co-Lab]; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-02; 8.5x11.
    7. The Cat Heads, Slovenly, Box O' Laffs; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-08; 8.5x11.
    8. Caroliner Rainbow Shit Of Sowlynx, Snotgreen Sea, Mudwomen [Mud Wombmen of Aphrodesia (ex-Frightwigger "Ra")], V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-03; 8.5x11.
    9. Lucas; Last Day Saloon; 406 Clement St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-18; 8.5x11.
    10. Ire and the Hardcores; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; February 27; 8.5x11.
    11. Interlopers, Keith Malaise; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-06; 8.5x11.
    12. The Invertebrates; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-03; 8.5x11.
    13. Impulse F, Permanent Wave; Bay Brick Inn; 1190 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-16; 8.5x11.
    14. Inner City; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-11; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 7, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Jackal, Bad Habit, Changeling; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; March [illegible]th; 8.5x11.
    2. Fan Club, Jackals; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; July 29; 8.5x11.
    3. Inverted Triangle, Teckno Fear; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; October 2; 8.5x11.
    4. Hunh! Funk Family Jammin; 16th Note/Firehouse 7; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    5. Fade To Black, Our Lady Of Pain, Napalm Beach, Thieves' Cross; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-31; 8.5x11.
    6. Honeymooners, 7 Dutch Poets; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-04; 8.5x11.
    7. Jeffrey Normal & Magick; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; November 27;1986-01-17; 8.5x11.
    8. What Is Real? [?], House Of Wheels; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-17; 8.5x11.
    9. Jet Boy; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-11; 8.5x11.
    10. Home Of The Brave, The Nice Boys from New York; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; January 30; 8.5x11.
    11. The Holy Sisters Of The Gaga Dada, X-Tal; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-15; 8.5x11.
    12. The Furies, The Hot Combs; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-28; 8.5x11.
    13. Processed World #16 Is Now In Stores; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 8, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Bad Habit, Morally Bankrupt, Armageddon Light Company, Films By J.R. Swansonn & Steve Mann; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-28; 8.5x11.
    2. Joan Armatrading; Berkeley Community Theatre [Berkeley Community Center]; 1900 Allston Way Berkeley, CA; 1985-05-25; 8.5x11.
    3. Connie Hatch, Serving The Status Quo, Incite! (Projected Photomontage), Scott Weber, Geographic Exorcism (Video Montage); New Generic; 2 Clinton Park San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-17; 8.5x11.
    4.[unidentified form, possible distorted medical photograph?]; 8.5x11.
    5. Third Wave; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-08; 8.5x11.
    6. Four Images Of Revolution, Time Of Daring; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-06; 8.5x11.
    7. The Toilet And The Baptism; Theatre Rhinoceros; 2926 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    8. Reno Invites Any Men Who Would like To Try Nude Modeling To Send A Letter And A Photo to Him at: [address]; San Francisco, CA; 8x8.5.
    9. Doug Wendt's Rockin' Steady Dance Party. DJ Doug Wendt and the Midnite Dread Sight And Sound System [March 19 & April 2 list performances at Wolfgang's]; Wolfgang's [Wolfgang Presents at Noma]; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; Wednesdays March 12, 19, 26, April 2, 9 1986; 8.5x11.
    10. One Man Band. Tim & T.J. [Tim Jones with puppet T.J. Hustler] Featuring Dianne (Former Ikette With Tina Turner) [Diane Candace]; Lucky Lion; 10 Hegenberger Rd. Oakland, CA; Every Friday & Saturday; 8.5x11.
    11. One Man Band. Tim & T.J. [Tim Jones with puppet T.J. Hustler] Featuring Dianne (Former Ikette With Tina Turner) [Diane Candace]; Sweet Jimmy's; 2273 Telegraph Ave. Oakland, CA; Every Wednesday; 8.5x11.
    12. One Man Band. Tim & T.J. [Tim Jones with puppet T.J. Hustler] Featuring Dianne (Former Ikette With Tina Turner) [Diane Candace]; Lena's New 4 Mile House; 5251 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; Every Thursday & Sunday; 8.5x11.
    13. Den 55; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-20; 8.5x11.
    14. Defect This Summer. USSR & Poland Tours. Council Travel Services 919 Irving St. San Francisco, CA; Summer 1986; 8.5x11.
    15. Images From South Africa. An International Art Show; Media; 360 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-18; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 9, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Judy Grahn; New College Gallery; 762 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-24; 8.5x11.
    2. Subterranean Video. S. Vid; Eye Gallery; 758 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-15; 8.5x11.
    3. Orlando Frizado, Pamela Wylie, Lora Moysard, Dirk Slater; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; Saturdays March 22, April 5, 26 1986; 8.5x11.
    4. Imagine Something Else. The Mary Club. Footwork In May; Footwork Studio; 3221 22nd St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    5. City Beat, 'Live' TV Talk Show. All About Vibrators. Good Vibrations. Information! Cable Channel 25; San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-09; 8.5x11.
    6. DFS. De Fiance Suction; Illustrated Stage; 595 Mission St. San Francisco, CA; February 11-27, March 3-6; 8.5x11.
    7. Lifestyle Clothing & Accessories. 10% Off With This Coupon; East Coast Girls; 2265 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    8. Subterranean Video. S. Vid; 8.5x11.
    9. Christos Dementia; California College of Art and Design (CCAD); San Francisco, CA; [March 22?]; 8.5x11.
    10. The Hippie Temptation, [with Psychedelic Shorts]; Red Vic Movie House; 1659 Haight St. San Francisco, CA;1985-01; 8.5x11.
    11. Robeski; The Bear; 440 Castro St. San Francisco, CA; April 6-June 1; 8.5x11.
    12. James Justin in "Novy Mir", Marlene Dietrich in "The Blue Angel"; New Generic; 2 Clinton Park San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-21; 8.5x11.
    13. Unknown Soldier Salutes The Doors, Brotherhood Of Light (Lightshow), Pearl, Tribute to Janis Joplin, Donn Jett, Elvis; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 10, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Bruce Geduldig & Winston Tong. Like The Others, A Work-In-Progress; Climate; 252 9th St. San Francisco, CA; March 6-9; 8.5x11.
    2. The Leopard Set, Denise Grimshaw (Poetry Performance); Baybrick Inn [Clementina's Baybrick Inn]; 1190 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-30; 8.5x11.
    3. Loud 3D. Hardcore Like You've Never Seen It. A Live Rock'n'Roll Action Book. By Gary Robert, Rob Kulakofsky & Mike Arredondo. 3D Glasses Included; IN3D; 5841 Geary Blvd. San Francisco, CA; 1984; 8.5x11.
    4. Gray Matter Collective. Bonnie, Monica, Chris, Johann [phone numbers]. Gray Matter Interests [looking for communal vegetarian household, continued production of the Daily Lobe & other art, theater, music]. Gray Matter Manifesto [etc.]; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    5. Dude Theatre. Atomic Motel; Club Nine [Nine]; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12; 8.5x11.
    6. Dega Ray, Jungle Book, Pamela Z, Spider Box; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-27; 8.5x11.
    7. Ntozake Shange; Lorraine Hansberry Theatre. In The Nave Of Trinity Episcopal Church; 1668 Bush St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-19; 8.5x11.
    8. Typhoon; Sofia's; 527 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-23; 8.5x11.
    9. Falling Dog. Dance Theatre Performance. Mary Trunk. Maxine Moerman; Video Free America; 442 Shotwell St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-24; 8.5x11.
    10. D.R.I., The Offenders, Sacrilege, Destiny; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1985-09-20; 8.5x11.
    11. Whorl, No Exit, The Union.; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-12; 8.5x11.
    12. Whorl; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-18; 8.5x11.
    13. Whorl; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-09; 8.5x11.
    15. The Finest In Metro Nightlife. After Hours Dancing. DJ: Alan Robinson; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 11, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)